I was extremely excited for "Spyro: Reignited".
Remember what I said in my Crash review?
"If Activision announces 'Spyro Remastered'
I will sacrifice a goat in their name."
So, was it worth it?
Because it turns out goats are not sheep.
(hehe haha)
Yes!
It's actually better than that other game.
I'll admit, I'm a bit biased.
I actually prefer Spyro over
[Brief pause]
Dark Souls.
So when the the time came, on launch day,
I woke up at five a.m.
I was gonna test the game for twenty minutes then do something productive.
Anyway, six hours later I had completed the first game.
Ugh... I was gonna have to 100% all three games on day one.
Is that possible? Yes, very.
But if you're gonna attempt it,
I recommend being something called "unemployed".
The first game I had never completed.
I had only played it at a neighbours house,
when they were asleep.
I would sneak in at night, play Spyro™,
and steal his Pokémon® cards.
That's why it took longer than expected,
because some of these dragons-
Well, let's just say I applaud the kids who managed to find them on their own.
And if you were this smart as a kid,
imagine how life could have turned out.
Really messed up, didn't you?
The only hard challenge is this flight challenge
that I'm guessing was designed by some grumpy Insomniac employee
that hates children.
And then he became the lead designer on the second game!
"Spyro 2: Gateway to
RAGE!"
I started the second game around lunchtime.
Completing all three games on day one is the most important challenge of my life.
But when you binge-play them like this
you really notice how much better Spyro 2 is,
and how much worse it is when you're attempting a day one 100% completion.
It's longer and for some reason
the remake is harder than back in the 90's.
Everything was harder in the 90's!
"I fell asleep to the movie, how do I restart it?"
I have completed the original, so I know where everything is,
but, uh... honestly I have to say:
this is what I remember it looking like when I was a kid.
I'm not even sure if they actually Remastered©™ this or if, uh...
they just did like "Dark Souls: 'Remastered'" and just improved the lighting.
First world: easy!
I am the top five Spyro player in this universe and all other universes!
Best game all time!
Second world:
fuck you!
Fuck you!
This game is bad! Worst game in the multiverse!
After experiencing exactly what a World War I veteran went through;
I made it to the second boss,
who I've never had any problems with.
He's destroying me! What th- what is this?
Last world: easy. Good game. I completed it.
And at this point only 0.3% have done that.
Makes me sad for humanity.
If you are not alone, binge-playing a 19-year-old children's game,
what are you doing with your life?
[Snarling]
You will never feel every second of enjoyment
I felt hurting these elephants.
Third game.
[Exhaling]
I was getting tired, and Spyro 3 is the hardest game in the series.
I hate how hard it can get.
They made it easy!
I hate how easy it gotten-get!
They nerfed my Spyro!
Nerfed is the wrong word.
Castrated! Activision castrated my purple dragon!
That's a sentence I hope I get to use again.
I remember getting this game for Christmas,
waking up the next morning,
and raging uncontrollably!
You don't mess with a man's rage-fuel!
First world: not a problem,
done it so many times I can probably do it with my eyes closed.
Without a controller.
Second world: easy, not even worth mentioning how easy it was;
that's how easy it was.
But the third world, ugh...
the third world has the hardest challenge in the Spyro franchise.
This one boss can make me rage-quit this entire challenge.
I was considering to...
take performance-enhancing drugs to beat him.
But they fixed it! Come on!
Have you never heard the saying: "don't fix what isn't isn't broken"?
But now there was nothing stopping me from getting 100%
and achieving something way more impressive than an olympic medal!
Third world. I was getting really tired,
but there was only one world left, so I decided to
go to sleep because it's healthier.
[Wacky outro music]
(remember to call Kilian a wuss in the comments)